= kissasia.co =
♪ From primal chaos to the starry sky ♪
♪ In the whole world, we shall hold the balance ♪
♪ The cauldron tempers divine blades ♪
♪ The furnace refines the empty void ♪
♪ The Way is in mystic fate ♪
♪ Be brave enough to split the primal chaos wide open ♪
[Pull Strings]
[Adapted from the novel by Yan Gui Zheng Zhuan]
[Episode 18]
Si'er?
It sees so far.
What magic instrument is this?
Telescope.
Telescope?
I've only heard of the Spell reveal Mirror.
Whose magic instrument is this?
Mine.
Yours?
Let me have a look.
One more look.
Bumpkin.
It's like the Farglass.
How did you know
they'd fight here today?
I set it up in secret.
Is that so?
Jiang Si'er knows Ao Yi well.
She'll surely recognize him.
And the Mermaid Clan just fell out
with the Dragon Clan.
Ao Yi
is sure to be her first target.
So, their fight today
was part of your plan, too?
Of course.
I just used Jiang Si'er
to test Ao Yi's true strength.
Because all my later plans
depend on a true read
of Ao Yi's strength.
So cautious, huh?
How's the evaluation?
Zero points.
Pathetic.
What?
What's that?
Mine.
This...
Just a habit, you see.
Mine.
I know, I know.
It's mine.
Are you crazy?
You can't have it.
Our clan had hoped
for your return to the East Sea,
and we'd support you to replace Ao Jia.
But you're so weak.
How can you save the Dragon Clan?
I...
What did you learn in the Mortal Realm?
Your martial arts,
magical power,
and quick wit
are all a mess.
No.
I
I was wrong.
I should not have expected more.
You're that spoiled little dragon
from the East Sea.
You'll never grow up.
You should go back to the East Sea.
Outside the East Sea,
you can't survive at all.
Are you here to take me back?
Take you back?
You can still return to the East Sea.
Yet our clan
has no home left.
What happened?
I broke off the engagement with your brother.
It enraged the Dragon Clan.
The Mermaid Clan has no place in the East Sea.
We can never go back.
I heard Changgeng the Great is at Ascendance Sect.
I wanted to bring my clan to seek his help.
But I don't know where he is now.
Once I master the Seizing Sect's arts,
I can take you back too.
You?
I've never seen a dragon as weak as you.
Don't bully Little Uncle!
You bold demoness!
How dare you strike a Seizing Sect disciple!
Zhao Gongming of Seizing Sect is on this mountain.
With one shout, he'll appear!
Is it time for my entrance?
Not yet. Don't rush.
No, she's calling my name.
Hold on. Don't rush.
Show me. Let me see.
Mine.
I know. I...
This is the Human Clan for you to learn from?
Little Uncle, are you all right?
I wanted to join Seizing Sect and study the Way,
so I could revive...
Was I
being too naive?
What nonsense.
You're not weak at all.
Are people born strong?
Even a sage
must learn step by step.
But I can't do anything.
That only means
you can learn anything.
Our mentor may be a bit lacking,
but he is a Seizing Sect deity.
As long as you're willing to learn,
you'll surely grow strong.
Besides, you're not fully healed yet.
Losing is only natural.
I'll brew you more medicine later.
Come on.
It really is your turn.
Here's your chance. Go.
It's mine.
Thank you.
It's mine!
Uncle Zhao, perfect timing.
Someone tried to bully Little Uncle.
Who is so bold
as to bully Seizing Sect members?
Exactly!
Go.
Lead the way, quickly.
I'll catch up with her.
I'll extort her to death.
Little Uncle.
I just got a telescope. Take a look.
It seems like the Farglass.
What telescope?
Bai Shi?
Bai Shi? It's not Bear Island.
Right,
Ke Le'er?
I'm Li Changshou.
Greetings, Ao Yi, Second Prince of the East Sea.
What do you want?
Though I have no magical power now...
Enough.
I know you have no magical power.
I saw your fight just now.
You saw it?
I had thought
you might last two rounds
and impress Jiang Si'er.
You...
Enough.
As you are, you can't fell a hen.
Go on. Take a rest.
If I were in Dragon Palace,
I'd defeat you with ease.
Enough.
When the two of us spar,
winning is easy; Losing is hard.
If it were not for me.
I've already
broken free of my bonds,
fulfilled Dragon's Prophecy,
and achieved dragon transformation.
But who could have known...
Well.
Do you remember what happened
after the dragon transformation?
After the dragon transformation?
I just remember.
Hua died right in front of me.
I felt a surge
of uncontrollable power rise inside me.
Then I lost consciousness.
Later, I woke up
on Turtle Island.
Senior Yuan Ze saved me.
You don't remember what happened
after the dragon transformation?
No.
But I remember
this one person
kept touching me
all over.
The Mortal Realm is terrifying.
It's full of shameless rogues.
Yes.
Yes, there are plenty of rogues.
There's another matter.
I lost the power of dragon transformation.
Power of dragon transformation?
Look.
What's wrong?
Your skin looks fine.
That's not the point!
I had a mark right here.
That was my Dragon's Prophecy.
Now, it's gone.
Dragon's Prophecy?
Why is this so hard to wash off?
Your Dragon's Prophecy is gone?
No, that thing
came off so easily?
Impossible.
What came off?
No, I mean, could it be
that it's just less visible now?
What are you doing?
I've accepted my Fated Mandate.
No, you can't accept this.
Could it be
transferred somewhere else?
Hurry!
It didn't transfer.
Let me see.
I've made up my mind.
The Dragon's Prophecy
is a curse to me.
Now, it's gone.
I can finally shed my dragon identity.
I've made my choice.
I will re-cultivate the Human Clan's Way.
This is my true Fated Mandate.
That was your lifeline!
If it's gone, what am I to do?
What did you just say?
I said
I've made up my mind
to study the Human Clan's spells.
That is my true Fated Mandate.
Human Clan's spells?
Exactly.
Even without the Dragon's Prophecy,
you can still restore your strength.
What you lack is spiritual power.
If I can replenish your spiritual power,
that's readily...
Your Highness.
I have a plan
to greatly boost your strength in no time.
That impressive?
But you must trust me.
I've never seen a dragon as weak as you.
Tell me. What should I do?
How long ago was the last time
we sat drinking together,
Senior?
I think it was
when my power just edged past yours.
That was so long ago.
I can barely remember.
Junior Kuai Si,
I know
you look down on me.
You think I'm completely useless.
But whether you see me as a bird in the sky,
a fish in the water,
or a sheep grazing in a field,
I don't care.
But if you move against my disciples,
I will fight you to the death.
Word has spread that the immortal seeding
who survived the Divine-Demon Tribulation
is called Changgeng,
yet no one has ever truly seen him.
Senior, have you thought
that perhaps
this person isn't Changgeng?
Maybe it's someone
we all know.
Such as...?
Your mentor
and Senior Wan Jiangyu
headed to the South Sea, right?
Time has passed.
There's been no word from them.
It couldn't be her.
What if.
I have a clue?
Mentor,
you want me
to attempt the formation trial?
Of course.
You won a great victory yesterday.
Today, you must press the advantage.
Do you truly think so?
Changshou,
our division has not shone in years.
Grandlord praised you yesterday.
Changshou,
do you feel that today,
I seem different too?
How so?
Don't you see my eyes are bright,
and my complexion looks better?
Most of all,
I stand straighter.
I don't see it.
What if I fail the formation trial?
Then so be it.
We've been in 800th place
in the Sect Competition for years.
Come on, little fish, bite.
After all morning, nothing.
Mentor.
Please think of a way yourself.
No, no, Changshou.
Changshou.
I...
Mentor.
I still think
you're not yourself today.
Not myself?
I'm the same as ever.
Are you?
I am.
Then, what if I tell you
I won't do the formation trial?
If you don't,
I'll expel you from the division.
Mentor,
confess honestly.
Who did you see last night? Where did you go?
No.
I'm the Lord of Jade Division.
I am your mentor.
I go wherever I please.
I see whomever I wish.
Mentor.
When you were out in the world,
did I ever question you?
Did I ever scold you?
Did I ever interfere?
Mentor.
You keep calling me Mentor.
You are my disciple.
Is one task too much to ask of my disciple?
I want everyone to respect Jade Division.
Is that so difficult?
If you refuse me,
don't call me Mentor anymore.
Yesterday...
Yesterday, I went to see Kuai Si.
What did he say to you?
What could he say?
He humiliated me, of course.
He called me a failure as a teacher,
saying Jade Division is worthless,
and we don't belong in Ascendance Sect.
You know what he's like.
He's been saying that for years.
It's fine.
Yes.
He's humiliated me all these years.
I thought those words
wouldn't faze me.
But when he actually said them,
each and every word
was like a knife,
stabbing my heart.
It hurts.
Changshou.
My good disciple.
All these years,
I've never asked you for anything.
Never.
Today, I beg you.
Please let our division
earn some respect for once.
I beg you.
Fine.
Changshou, I knew you'd understand.
Mentor, just stay here quietly.
Don't go anywhere.
Wait till I return defeated.
Then I'll undo the Transformation Art.
Good.
Changshou.
It's settled now.
A bit too settled.
It looks like a fish took the bait.
The Formation Assembly begins.
Disciples of all sects,
please enter in an orderly manner.
[Hall of Mystic Truth] Great!
Where's Mentor? Have you seen Mentor?
He hasn't come?
Has he come? I couldn't find him.
What are we waiting for, Uncle?
Wait...
Well.
Let's wait and see.
Don't worry, Little Uncle.
If she shows up again tonight,
our Seizing Sect can deal with her.
Okay.
Isn't she...
The Mermaid Clan's Pearl Elites
are here for the Formation Assembly.
Let's begin.
Mentor,
why are a few missing?
Where is Aunt Jiu Jiu?
She got drunk
and caused trouble yesterday.
It nearly dragged Ascendance Sect
into a clash with Seizing Sect,
so Mentor sent her on mountain patrol.
Mountain patrol?
♪ Jiu Jiu patrols the hills today ♪
♪ I roam these mountains all the way ♪
What is it, Aunt?
Feeling down?
No.
What? You know I am leaving,
and you're missing me already?
Of course.
Without you here,
I will feel unsafe.
It is just mountain patrol.
I will be back tomorrow.
Here.
A gift from me.
This treasure may only be taken out
when no one else is around.
Have a taste.
Such a lovely aroma.
How is it?
Truly fine wine.
You're the best.
Thank you.
What's this?
This is
a little trinket
I made in my spare time.
It's called Sensing Stone.
Sensing Stone?
What does it do?
It monitors the surroundings
for any other spiritual sense.
See? It's light cyan now.
If it turns a darker shade,
there's a spiritual sense nearby.
For detecting dried corpses?
For detecting spiritual sense.
Oh, spiritual sense.
This is interesting
and rather pretty.
Grandlord has never sent anyone on mountain patrol as punishment.
Punishing you this way
must have a deeper purpose.
Perhaps he fears something.
Anyway, Aunt,
keep that stone on you.
Be careful in all things.
Are you worried about me?
I'm quite strong.
I can tell.
It's just mountain patrol.
I'll be back soon.
This is the Ascendance Sect.
Let me see who dares cause trouble here.
Lingli, you're so heavy.
Lingli, you've gained weight again.
Shut up.
When do we begin?
Have you found our Grandlord yet?
Almost. Almost.
This pearl
is forged by the Elucidating Sect.
Anyone with an intact foundation
can get millennium spiritual power from this.
Whoever finds this pearl
will pass the formation
and get the pearl.
Who'd want that treasure? Honestly.
All the beings in the world.
Rise!
Not bad.
Who'll try
the formation trial first?
Mentor.
I'm Youqin Xuanya of Skyrend Division, Ascendance Sect.
I request entry to the formation.
Okay.
Go ahead.
I see.
The Elucidating Sect's formation is truly profound.
Who else
dares to enter the picture?
Forget it.
Please, Junior.
Tomorrow,
you must challenge Cloudlink Hermit's formation.
I...
Don't you want to recover your strength?
I do,
but...
The reason you have no power now is
that an old rogue
stripped away all your spiritual power.
If you can just replenish your spiritual power,
you'll at least recover
to the level you had at Dragon Palace.
That makes sense.
But what does my formation trial
have to do with my spiritual power?
Don't worry about that.
Leave it to me.
I have a way.
I'll do it.
Are you crazy?
Senior said
that Turtle Island disciples can lose,
but they can't back down.
Right, Senior?
Well said.
Come on.
I'll help you.
Thanks, Senior.
Right, right. We can back down...
We can lose, but not back down.
Go on.
Then why aren't you two going?
I'm not feeling well.
Besides, I'm not the one going.
I'm out of weapons.
Yes, yes.
Senior,
I'll go first.
Watch out for safety.
Nonsense.
Watch out for danger!
I'm a disciple of Turtle Island,
here to attempt the formation trial.
Wait.
I'm Hanzhi, disciple of Turtle Island,
here to enter the formation as well.
Girl.
Learn from Turtle Island.
Good, good.
Learn.
Who else
wants to test their mettle in the formation trial?
Anyway, I dare not go.
I'm not going either.
Senior,
who do you think will go first?
Mistveil or Griefbane?
Senior, you.
I'm Li Changshou of Jade Division.
I request to enter the array.
Good.
Go on.
Little rascal, be careful.
Rest easy, Yunxiao.
Who else?
Someone else went in.
Is it our Grandlord?
I don't know.
I can't see his face.
I don't know who it is.
A Jade disciple went in.
Why are we still standing here?
Yeah.
This is Ascendance Sect.
Let's go.
I'm Wang Qi of Spiritkin Division,
requesting to enter the formation.
I'm Liu Sizhe of Spiritkin Division,
Go on.
Why are you still standing there?
Go over there.
That hurts!
Let's go.
♪ Once a drifting weed, I loved to roam ♪
♪ Now, a levee holds back the storm ♪
♪ Fight against fate for my life ♪
♪ Close eyes to sense the world ♪
♪ Years splash ink ♪
♪ Trekking far and wide ♪
♪ Silent in subtleties ♪
♪ The task descends on me ♪
♪ Though millions block, it echoes loud ♪
Help! Help!
♪ Plain and unremarkable ♪
Help!
♪ If smooth, seek peace ♪
♪ Mad ones, why ruin your foundation ♪
♪ The evil knows no shame ♪
♪ Immortal trials burn cowardice away ♪
Yunxiao!
♪ Gouging eyes to light the night and ferry souls ♪
Did you have fun?
Yes.
Thank you for your help.
That's why I manage with such ease.
♪ Today my name reaches heaven ♪
♪ Actually, I've descended to the world ♪
Yunxiao,
how do you know Cloudlink Hermit's formation?
I've passed it three times.
You've been here?
I think I took his Fiend scour Mirror
and never gave it back.
Turn right up ahead.
All right.
♪ Charging against the wind ♪
♪ Old scars reveal the truth ♪
Turn right?
No way.
I'd better evade.
Evade.
♪ I temper a clear conscience ♪
Senior.
♪ I won't yield ♪
Even this formation
can't reveal your true skill?
Little Uncle!
Girl.
Senior.
Your Highness, strike a pose.
Pose?
What do you mean?
Well.
Just strike a pose.
Why are these swords circling me?
The move I lent him
should not be seen through, right?
Junior Youqin,
among our Three Sects,
this rivalry and tense air
is hardly good, is it?
Yeah.
We all cultivate the Way.
We should help one another.
Why fight to rank above others?
Exactly.
On the path of immortality,
bonds always matter.
Your words
are truly worth savoring.
I have an idea.
It can raise Ascendance Sect's renown
and turn Seizing Sect from foe to friend.
Senior, just give the word.
I want you to step forth
to challenge.
Cloudlink Hermit's formation.
I want you to aid
the Seizing cultivator.
As you two work together,
everyone will see
that sects joining hands
can wield far greater power.
Well.
To repel foes with you
is my greatest honor.
Your skills are truly remarkable.
I'm deeply impressed.
How formidable.
Your disciple?
I taught him.
He has newly developed magic arts.
Really?
They're even more powerful.
I don't believe it.
Could Changgeng be one of these two?
Where do we go next?
Senior Changshou,
we'll follow your lead.
There's a mountain to your east.
The treasure sits atop the peak.
Alright.
Sir,
please.
♪ I don't ask, too lazy to fight ♪
♪ I dare to live my own way ♪
♪ In the Primordial World ♪
♪ Who sings and drinks free ♪
♪ The stars smile at fireflies ♪
Why do we get all the dirty work
while he hides underground?
He's always been like this.
He does all the work himself,
yet we get the credit.
I see.
Fame means nothing to me.
I seek only the way of life.
Break the formation together. Got it?
Yes.
I never thought
this Seizing cultivator's technique
is so similar to our ways.
It seems all paths share one origin.
I didn't know he was so powerful.
Yesterday,
was he going easy on me?
Our clan may finally have hope.
But I'm the senior.
Right?
Yes, yes.
You don't think Little Uncle
has fallen for her, right?
No, no.
Little Uncle is still a child, right?
Can you do anything besides nodding?
You think this can break my formation?
You underestimate me.
Soul Projection!
Senior,
we've reached the summit.
Junior, block the demon beast
and buy us some time.
Understood.
What are you standing there for?
Hurry, find the treasure!
Over there.
Hey.
I won't let you
break the formation so easily.
Come on.
Face the formation trial!
Who knew he'd cheat when losing?
Changshou, what do we do now?
Don't panic.
If he can cheat, so can I.
Where are you?
Face the formation trial!
What's going on?
Changshou,
weren't you going to help me seize spiritual power?
I'll keep my word.
If we hide here,
how do we get that pearl?
Who says you need the pearl for spiritual power?
But...
When painting,
a cultivator will unconsciously infuse
their cultivation insights into it,
forming Resonance.
Grasping Resonance can help you draw spiritual power.
So, the moment you entered,
you were already drawing it in.
I see.
You had a plan.
Close your eyes.
Recall all the scenery
you saw on the way.
Wait.
Why am I the only one comprehending?
Why are you not?
Because I am slow.
And you are gifted.
Fair enough.
Think carefully.
Try to comprehend
the Resonance.
The tables have turned.
Cloudlink Hermit has played long enough.
Time for me to tease him with the formation.
This kid knows what Resonance is for.
A fine immortal seedling indeed.
This is...
He saw me use Mountain-Moving
and figured out
the secret of my Ream Landscape.
Good.
He even means to trap me.
I drew this landscape myself.
How could I not break out?
So, this is the Mortal Realm?
Indeed it is.
The Mortal Realm is perilous.
I must find Changgeng the Great
and take him as my mentor.
Wait.
Is learning from Changgeng so vital?
Of course, it is.
Only Changgeng the Great can train me,
so I can revive the Dragon Clan.
Answer me:
What good is strength?
The Dragon Clan used to be mighty,
but now, it's weakened.
The Demon Emperor swept the Three Realms,
yet he was defeated and met death.
Listen.
No matter how strong you are,
you cannot stand alone
against the whole world.
A true powerhouse
is not strong in themselves,
but in the people's hearts.
The people's hearts?
If you want to be Dragon Clan's light,
you don't need a mentor.
You need to be a leader
who can win over
the whole Dragon Clan.
Remember:
Without hearts, might is useless.
One who wins people's hearts is a hero.
People's hearts?
What if I lack people's hearts?
Will a dragon's heart do?
He has exceptional comprehension,
but his aesthetic sense is awful.
What kind
of brutal cultivation
has he endured?
I gathered many herbs
to make a custom sachet for you.
Take it out and sniff it now and then.
Perhaps one day, your sense of smell will come back.
Where did you get this sachet?
I was...
I...
Since I ran into that old rogue,
my sense of smell was gone.
My condolences.
No need, no need.
Senior can cure this.
Senior gave me this sachet.
She told me to keep it on me
and sniff it now and then.
Then, my sense of smell would return.
Has it come back?
Not at all.
But when I smell this,
I can faintly catch a scent.
What did you smell?
I smelled
that Changgeng the Great is in Ascendance Sect.
I must take him as my mentor.
Here he is.
Though I don't know.
Changgeng's true face,
as long as Changgeng is here,
the Pregenesis Sword
must be right here.
Elder Kuai,
it is time.
♪ See mortal joys and sorrows ♪
♪ Reunions and partings, as fate unfolds ♪
♪ Alas, love has many twists and turns ♪
♪ Memories filled with sorrow ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tearfully, this life's bond is not over ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪
♪ Down a few more cups of wine ♪
♪ Through land and sea, I ask you to come ♪
♪ For honor's sake, upright and grand ♪
♪ Alas, our story is short ♪
♪ Slowly, wishes turn to regret ♪
♪ You've gone afar, like mist fading ♪
♪ Tears fall, this fate's not done ♪
♪ Past fragments vanish into night ♪